<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Net-Stuff on bwoe</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/net-stuff/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Net-Stuff on bwoe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 16:31:03 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/net-stuff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Back to Letterboxd</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/back-to-letterboxd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 16:31:03 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/back-to-letterboxd/</guid>
      <description>In 2017-2018 I had an account on Letterboxd and a film buff phase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pain of Exploits</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-pain-of-exploits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 20:23:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-pain-of-exploits/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe this loathsome world.&#xA;While the blocklists I mentioned earlier are incredibly vital for trying to live day to day without the sense of near-apocalyptic dread, there is a certain flaw which I like to call&amp;hellip;&#xA;EXPLOITS I heard that some news of one of my favourite games getting downloadable content, but with the &amp;lsquo;Digital Benzodiazepine&amp;rsquo; blocklist added, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t learn anything about it on my main computer. I deleted the browser from my phone, so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use that either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About My Blocklists</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/about-blocklists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 16:39:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/about-blocklists/</guid>
      <description>In an earlier post, I explained how I used Cold Turkey Blocker to keep me sane. Today I&amp;rsquo;ll go over the blocklists I use and how I cycle between them for maximum efficiency and sanity-preservation.&#xA;Digital Duloxetine This blocklist is permanent, 24/7, until Cold Turkey is uninstalled (in other words, a system reset). It consists of of over 500 websites, ranging from garbage clickbait sites to pornography to central social media platforms to news outlets and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Internet Is Hell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-internet-is-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:42:48 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-internet-is-hell/</guid>
      <description>God bless Cold Turkey Blocker. What would I do without you? Well, live in a more honest world, an honestly shittier world. In my blocklist called &amp;lsquo;Digital Alprazolam&amp;rsquo; which lasts for the end of time and cannot be deactivated without uninstalling Cold Turkey. I have blocked 500+ sites, including popular social media psyop tools like Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn and the like. If I need to apply for a job with LinkedIn, then I&amp;rsquo;ll stay unemployed, thank you very much.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
