<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Net-Stuff on bwoe</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/net-stuff/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Net-Stuff on bwoe</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 12:48:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/net-stuff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I Blocked Almost Every Site for a Year - This is What Happened</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/blocked-almost-every-site-for-a-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 12:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/blocked-almost-every-site-for-a-year/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So in my posts &lt;a href=&#34;../the-internet-is-hell&#34;&gt;The Internet is Hell&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;../about-blocklists&#34;&gt;About My Blocklists&lt;/a&gt;, I explained a strategy that I was taking for the year: extreme isolation from the ebb and flow of the internet using Cold Turkey Blocker and a generous amount of browser extensions. I should also add that I installed browser extensions like uBlacklist to block search engine results, Shut Up to block comments, etc. Extreme measures, but measures that I thought would improve my mental health and distance me from the noise of the 2020s Information Age.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blocklist After a Week</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/blocklist-after-a-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 11:29:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/blocklist-after-a-week/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, I had a week where I essentially had no internet apart from a few crucial sites after I decided to mess around with &lt;a href=&#34;https://getcoldturkey.com/&#34;&gt;Cold Turkey Blocker&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After the blocklist was finally disabled, I thought I would feel _. It was a boring week, filled with anxiety _.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But now, I just feel numb.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not just because of the bad news and _ discourse, but because it made me feel some sort of way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blocklists Never Again</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/blocklists-never-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 14:46:22 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/blocklists-never-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I found a way to disable my blocklists, and I used it to browse some YT videos to see the comments/responses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;/Never again./&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Never. Ever. Again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The worst part about it is, even in an innocent comment thread - like in a highly liked comment praising something you like or something you support, you click the ‘show more comments’ thread with the _ knowing full well that there’ll be something negative. That there’ll be something awful, that there’ll be a comment that tells you that the thing you like or support or &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; are garbage, and so on. Like nothing is safe. And when you click it, thinking maybe, just maybe, this time it’ll be okay? But of course, it never is. Your pessimism is always correct.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pain of Exploits</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-pain-of-exploits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 20:23:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-pain-of-exploits/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t believe this loathsome world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the &lt;a href=&#34;../about-blocklists&#34;&gt;blocklists I mentioned earlier&lt;/a&gt; are incredibly vital for trying to live day to day without the sense of near-apocalyptic dread, there is a certain flaw which I like to call&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;exploits&#34;&gt;EXPLOITS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I heard that some news of one of my favourite games getting downloadable content, but with the &amp;lsquo;Digital Benzodiazepine&amp;rsquo; blocklist added, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t learn anything about it on my main computer. I deleted the browser from my phone, so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use that either. Like a crack addict needing his next hit, I pondered desperately how to CONSUME this ARBITRARY MEDIA until I found it - my Steam Deck. The Deck uses Linux, but I don&amp;rsquo;t use the desktop mode that often. Going into game mode and browsing through to find the game and the news, I saw something awful - a YouTube link.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About My Blocklists</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/about-blocklists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 16:39:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/about-blocklists/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In an &lt;a href=&#34;../the-internet-is-hell&#34;&gt;earlier post&lt;/a&gt;, I explained how I used Cold Turkey Blocker to keep me sane. Today I&amp;rsquo;ll go over the blocklists I use and how I cycle between them for maximum efficiency and sanity-preservation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Digital Duloxetine&#xA;This blocklist is permanent, 24/7, until Cold Turkey is uninstalled (in other words, a system reset). It consists of of over 500 websites, ranging from garbage clickbait sites to pornography to central social media platforms to news outlets and beyond. There is no way to access these sites, so I can&amp;rsquo;t access them whatsoever. Good!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Internet Is Hell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-internet-is-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:42:48 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-internet-is-hell/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;God bless &lt;a href=&#34;https://getcoldturkey.com/&#34;&gt;Cold Turkey Blocker&lt;/a&gt;. What would I do without you? Well, live in a more honest world, an honestly shittier world. In my blocklist called &amp;lsquo;Digital Alprazolam&amp;rsquo; which lasts for the end of time and cannot be deactivated without uninstalling Cold Turkey. I have blocked 500+ sites, including popular social media psyop tools like Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn and the like. If I need to apply for a job with LinkedIn, then I&amp;rsquo;ll stay unemployed, thank you very much.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
