<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Other on bwoe</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/other/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Other on bwoe</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:30:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/other/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Late Year Update - Been a While</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/late-year-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/late-year-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been two months since I’ve updated the blog. I have a lot on my mind, so let me just compose my thoughts like this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had a period of depression. I can’t really articulate how bad it was (still is?), so I&amp;rsquo;ll talk about it another time; it was the worst I&amp;rsquo;ve felt in such a long time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m not really quite sure what to do with the future. I don’t have much faith for 2025; I feel like all avenues for self-improvement have been exhausted. Seriously, what can I do? Sometimes I think I should do a reviewing site to keep my fingertips warm, or expand my social media, or compose music, but then the thought is crushed some way or another. So I’m seriously conflicted. I need to figure out something before the end of the year, seriously.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barred From Expeditions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/barred-from-expeditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 17:31:06 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/barred-from-expeditions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t been in a proper photography expedition since &lt;a href=&#34;../aylesbury-expedition&#34;&gt;Aylesbury&lt;/a&gt;, and the reason is quite embarrassing, but I&amp;rsquo;ll say it upfront; I haven&amp;rsquo;t had hot water in my house for over TWO WEEKS.  Fortunately it&amp;rsquo;s summer, but that also means no hot showers. I like to wake up super early (before morning rush hour) and then travel to do my expeditions, which involves hours of long exploratory walks; I can&amp;rsquo;t do that with no showers. And my family is a little bit too far away to use theirs. I&amp;rsquo;ve never been kind of those people are extremely anxious about BO and layer themselves with deodorant, but this is just impossible. There are no more expeditions unless my landlord gets their shit together and fixes it. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I&amp;rsquo;m being robbed of these finest summer months because of it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Much Needed Update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/a-much-needed-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:05:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/a-much-needed-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been &amp;lsquo;away&amp;rsquo; for a while. Okay, it&amp;rsquo;s only been two weeks since my last blog post, but a lot has happened. Anxiety over the news and family situations has resulted in me relapsing in a reclusive state, doing nothing but lying in my bed playing video games. But hey, &lt;a href=&#34;../../game/game-fatigue-gone/&#34;&gt;at least I&amp;rsquo;m playing video games for once!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because of this, I haven&amp;rsquo;t gone on an &amp;rsquo;expedition&amp;rsquo; like I promised, but I did go on a quick stroll to capture the sunrise one day while listening to the newly shadow-dropped Parannoul album. Didn&amp;rsquo;t get as many endorphins as I hoped, but I&amp;rsquo;m okay with the results.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phantom Pain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/phantom-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 15:22:50 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/phantom-pain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t updated the blog in a while because I was sick for a while - aches and headaches all over. But today I feel normal. And of course, when there&amp;rsquo;s fever, there&amp;rsquo;s fever dreams. And last night&amp;rsquo;s fever dream was something else.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Basically, I was panicking because of university deadlines. I was thinking to myself, what if I repeat the year &lt;em&gt;again&lt;/em&gt;? How can I be 20+ years and still in university? How many black waves do I have to suffer to achieve my education? I imagined the student debt piling up, receiving no honours by the end of the year due to poor performance and having my CVs shredded, the image of the campus being burned in my retinas for eternity, just a nightmare of educational bureaucracy suffocating me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
