<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bwoe</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on bwoe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:42:21 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Play Videoverse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/play-videoverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:42:21 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/play-videoverse/</guid>
      <description>One day, I decided to check OpenCritic, a Metacritic-like video game rating aggregation site, for the _ hunt for hidden gems. I discovered two highly-rated games that I&amp;rsquo;ve never heard before. One was &amp;lsquo;Vernal Edge&amp;rsquo;, a unique but pretty boring Metroidvania. The other, though, is a contender for one of the greatest pieces of interactive media I&amp;rsquo;ve ever had the luxury of experiencing.&#xA;Videoverse is part-social simulation, part-visual novel. Designed as a love letter to old video game message boards and social platforms, Videoverse revolves around the titular social network, an amalgation of GameSpy and Miiverse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worried Since 2019</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/worried-since-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:16:08 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/worried-since-2019/</guid>
      <description>One of my biggest faults is that I worry way too much. I think a lot of that has to do with OCD, but after months and months of fluoxetine treatment, I think there&amp;rsquo;s something bigger at play. A lot of the time, my worries are realized. I worried in 2019 about the centralised Web and the existence of algorithmic radicalisation. In worried in 2020 about the impact of COVID. I worried in 2021 and 2022 about post-pandemic malaise, and that virulent populism will surge as a result of widespread vaccine controversy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pain of Exploits</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-pain-of-exploits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 20:23:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-pain-of-exploits/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe this loathsome world.&#xA;While the blocklists I mentioned earlier are incredibly vital for trying to live day to day without the sense of near-apocalyptic dread, there is a certain flaw which I like to call&amp;hellip;&#xA;EXPLOITS I heard that some news of one of my favourite games getting downloadable content, but with the &amp;lsquo;Digital Benzodiazepine&amp;rsquo; blocklist added, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t learn anything about it on my main computer. I deleted the browser from my phone, so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use that either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phantom Pain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/phantom-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 15:22:50 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/phantom-pain/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t updated the blog in a while because I was sick for a while - aches and headaches all over. But today I feel normal. And of course, when there&amp;rsquo;s fever, there&amp;rsquo;s fever dreams. And last night&amp;rsquo;s fever dream was something else.&#xA;Basically, I was panicking because of university deadlines. I was thinking to myself, what if I repeat the year again? How can I be 20+ years and still in university?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Black Waves</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/the-black-waves/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:24:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/the-black-waves/</guid>
      <description>In the beginning of 2023, I brought a sparkling new Macbook Pro and a subscription to Day One, and started a blog - Magdi Battles the Black Waves. It was intended to last for a year, but I only managed to keep track until August.&#xA;This was intended not for entertainment, but to help me manage my life. bwoe stands for &amp;lsquo;Black Waves of Energy&amp;rsquo;. What are black waves of energy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photography at the London MCM Expo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/photography-at-mcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:57:54 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/photography-at-mcm/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend was Comic Con day, and I know what that meant - lots and lots of cosplay photography to practice my portraits. Last year I went on a Friday, but today I decided to go on a Saturday. Big mistake. The venue was absolutely packed, completely crowded with cosplayers. You&amp;rsquo;d think this would be a good thing, but since Saturday opens very early (9am), I didn&amp;rsquo;t get much sleep. The lack of sleep to wake up for priority opening means less energy (and nerves&amp;hellip;) to ask for photos, plus the over-excess of cosplayers making my head spin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About My Blocklists</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/about-blocklists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 16:39:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/about-blocklists/</guid>
      <description>In an earlier post, I explained how I used Cold Turkey Blocker to keep me sane. Today I&amp;rsquo;ll go over the blocklists I use and how I cycle between them for maximum efficiency and sanity-preservation.&#xA;Digital Duloxetine This blocklist is permanent, 24/7, until Cold Turkey is uninstalled (in other words, a system reset). It consists of of over 500 websites, ranging from garbage clickbait sites to pornography to central social media platforms to news outlets and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See My Photos at Flickr!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/my-flickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:14:50 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/my-flickr/</guid>
      <description>&#xA;https://www.flickr.com/blackwavesofenergy </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still Fatigued</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/still-fatigued/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 17:25:17 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/still-fatigued/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been about a week since my rant about the closure of Tango Gameworks, and while I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten over it a bit, I&amp;rsquo;m still fatigued by gaming. With the announcement of the Switch successor, we&amp;rsquo;re inching towards a proper new generation of gaming, but it&amp;rsquo;s hard to be excited. Constant layoffs and studio closures. Rising prices and a trend towards $70 games. Cheaper budget games taken hostage by the whims of what popular streamers decide to play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Closure of Tango Gameworks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/the-closure-of-tango/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 18:20:23 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/the-closure-of-tango/</guid>
      <description>In early 2023, I felt like gaming wasn&amp;rsquo;t fun anymore. I knew it was a common fatigue though, and that there&amp;rsquo;ll be a game that I&amp;rsquo;ll play soon that would inject that fun and soul only the medium could provide. That happened when Hi-Fi Rush shadow dropped in January 2023. With its gorgeous Futurama-esque aesthetics and comedic tone and excellent reviews, I bought it and fell in love immediately. The catharsis of the character action and rhythm genres, joined at last in spectacular fashion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Internet Is Hell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-internet-is-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:42:48 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-internet-is-hell/</guid>
      <description>God bless Cold Turkey Blocker. What would I do without you? Well, live in a more honest world, an honestly shittier world. In my blocklist called &amp;lsquo;Digital Alprazolam&amp;rsquo; which lasts for the end of time and cannot be deactivated without uninstalling Cold Turkey. I have blocked 500+ sites, including popular social media psyop tools like Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn and the like. If I need to apply for a job with LinkedIn, then I&amp;rsquo;ll stay unemployed, thank you very much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citra and Yuzu are gone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/citra-yuzu-gone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 23:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/citra-yuzu-gone/</guid>
      <description>Well, damn. It was literally just yesterday that I uploaded about emulation problems, but now we have a different type of emulation problem: Citra and Yuzu are gone.&#xA;This is relevant because I was talking about a fatal bug for Dolphin, which also affected Citra (and RPCS3). The fix for Citra was uploaded LITERALLY YESTERDAY, meaning had the Citra/Yuzu team (the same dev team) hadn&amp;rsquo;t updated it, the last version of Citra on Flathub would be forever unbootable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flatpak Emu Problems of March 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/flatpak-emu-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/flatpak-emu-problems/</guid>
      <description>So recently, there was some bizarre emulation problems. The issue didn&amp;rsquo;t come with the Steam Deck, or EmuDeck, but with the emulators themselves, specifically the Flatpak version commonly used in Linux.&#xA;Dolphin, RPCS3, and Citra all were nonfunctional out of nowhere. Citra was quickly patched, but Dolphin and RPCS3 are still unable to boot as of this post. Booting them reveals no error message or dumped log. Booting them via CLI (i.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings for Citra</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/citra-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/citra-settings/</guid>
      <description>Playing 3DS games on a single screen can be tough. The vertical form factor of the 3DS makes gaming quite the challenge when emulating. So, these are my preferred Citra settings. Feel free to use or improve them.&#xA;Picross 3D Main screen: bottom Other screen: small or disabled Use a mouse and keyboard for this one, with d-pad and L buttons being used for controls. Other screen is not required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 16:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello World!&#xA;Tables of Contents Headers Emphasis Lists Links and Images Code Blocks Blockquotes Tables Horizontal Rules Line Breaks Escaping Characters Inline HTML Task Lists Subscripts and Superscripts Footnotes Automatic URL Linking Strikethrough Tables of Contents Headers Header 1 Header 2 Header 3 Header 4 Emphasis Bold text. Italic text. Bold and italic.&#xA;Lists Ordered list item 1. Ordered list item 2. Unordered list item 1 Unordered list item 2 Links and Images Link to Google Code Blocks public static void main(String[] args) { System.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>bwoe, aka Magdi, is a 27-year-old photographer, graphic designer, web developer, video game fanatical, university dropout, guitarist, cinephile, and general nutcase.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
