<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on bwoe</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on bwoe</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:30:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Late Year Update - Been a While</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/late-year-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/late-year-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been two months since I’ve updated the blog. I have a lot on my mind, so let me just compose my thoughts like this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had a period of depression. I can’t really articulate how bad it was (still is?), so I&amp;rsquo;ll talk about it another time; it was the worst I&amp;rsquo;ve felt in such a long time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m not really quite sure what to do with the future. I don’t have much faith for 2025; I feel like all avenues for self-improvement have been exhausted. Seriously, what can I do? Sometimes I think I should do a reviewing site to keep my fingertips warm, or expand my social media, or compose music, but then the thought is crushed some way or another. So I’m seriously conflicted. I need to figure out something before the end of the year, seriously.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryujinx Has Fallen</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/ryujinx-has-fallen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 16:48:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/ryujinx-has-fallen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I wrote about games, but it comes with some more bitter news. &lt;a href=&#34;../citra-yuzu-gone&#34;&gt;Citra and Yuzu were struck down by Nintendo earlier this year&lt;/a&gt;, and thus for seven months, Ryujinx was the only updated Nintendo Switch emulator. They were far more discreet than the Yuzu development team, and were also not based in the US, so it was expected that the Ryujinx team would hold out from Nintendo&amp;rsquo;s legal team, especially in the grey area that is video game emulation. But alas, it was not to be. While there was no lawsuit, the lead developer had arranged with Nintendo to shut down the project, sparing them any headaches.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blocklist After a Week</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/blocklist-after-a-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 11:29:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/blocklist-after-a-week/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, I had a week where I essentially had no internet apart from a few crucial sites after I decided to mess around with &lt;a href=&#34;https://getcoldturkey.com/&#34;&gt;Cold Turkey Blocker&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After the blocklist was finally disabled, I thought I would feel _. It was a boring week, filled with anxiety _.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But now, I just feel numb.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not just because of the bad news and _ discourse, but because it made me feel some sort of way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cobham Expedition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/cobham-expedition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 12:28:10 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/cobham-expedition/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s midday. I&amp;rsquo;m tired as shit, I woke up at 4am, I&amp;rsquo;ve spending the past few days tiring myself out trying to rearrange my house to accommodate family, and I&amp;rsquo;m on a train to Stoke &amp;amp; Cobham, on the shitty South Western Railway. For a train that takes you to posh-arse Surrey, it sure is a disaster of a train service. No air conditioning, old and dirty carriages, not even a tray on the seats. But there&amp;rsquo;s a short spell of sun - a week of natural light - and I need to make the most of it before the autumn clouds destroy what&amp;rsquo;s left of the summer. (Of course, it&amp;rsquo;s not like photography has a time limit, but I got to wait for autumn foliage to make the most of the season.)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blocklists Never Again</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/blocklists-never-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 14:46:22 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/blocklists-never-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I found a way to disable my blocklists, and I used it to browse some YT videos to see the comments/responses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;/Never again./&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Never. Ever. Again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The worst part about it is, even in an innocent comment thread - like in a highly liked comment praising something you like or something you support, you click the ‘show more comments’ thread with the _ knowing full well that there’ll be something negative. That there’ll be something awful, that there’ll be a comment that tells you that the thing you like or support or &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; are garbage, and so on. Like nothing is safe. And when you click it, thinking maybe, just maybe, this time it’ll be okay? But of course, it never is. Your pessimism is always correct.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September Thoughts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/september-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 10:42:01 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/september-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another much needed post. Once again, miscellaneous troubles cause hesitancy to update. Stress, anxiety and insomnia has come back full force, derailing any plans I had for the month. The end of summer and colder weather has also obstructed my usual photography opportunities. It&amp;rsquo;s been over a month since I&amp;rsquo;ve picked up my camera, and longer still since my last expedition in Aylesbury.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now I&amp;rsquo;m realising how important those photo expeditions were for my mental health. Without them, that feeling is more and more alien. If there&amp;rsquo;s anything I have to a hobby that I inherently love, it&amp;rsquo;s that. I don&amp;rsquo;t know why and how photography became such an important part of my regimen.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barred From Expeditions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/barred-from-expeditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 17:31:06 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/barred-from-expeditions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t been in a proper photography expedition since &lt;a href=&#34;../aylesbury-expedition&#34;&gt;Aylesbury&lt;/a&gt;, and the reason is quite embarrassing, but I&amp;rsquo;ll say it upfront; I haven&amp;rsquo;t had hot water in my house for over TWO WEEKS.  Fortunately it&amp;rsquo;s summer, but that also means no hot showers. I like to wake up super early (before morning rush hour) and then travel to do my expeditions, which involves hours of long exploratory walks; I can&amp;rsquo;t do that with no showers. And my family is a little bit too far away to use theirs. I&amp;rsquo;ve never been kind of those people are extremely anxious about BO and layer themselves with deodorant, but this is just impossible. There are no more expeditions unless my landlord gets their shit together and fixes it. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I&amp;rsquo;m being robbed of these finest summer months because of it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Much Needed Update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/a-much-needed-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:05:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/a-much-needed-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been &amp;lsquo;away&amp;rsquo; for a while. Okay, it&amp;rsquo;s only been two weeks since my last blog post, but a lot has happened. Anxiety over the news and family situations has resulted in me relapsing in a reclusive state, doing nothing but lying in my bed playing video games. But hey, &lt;a href=&#34;../../game/game-fatigue-gone/&#34;&gt;at least I&amp;rsquo;m playing video games for once!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because of this, I haven&amp;rsquo;t gone on an &amp;rsquo;expedition&amp;rsquo; like I promised, but I did go on a quick stroll to capture the sunrise one day while listening to the newly shadow-dropped Parannoul album. Didn&amp;rsquo;t get as many endorphins as I hoped, but I&amp;rsquo;m okay with the results.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Fatigue Ends</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/game-fatigue-gone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:05:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/game-fatigue-gone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sometime around 2 July, my gaming fatigue disappeared. The Steam Summer sale and an increase of mood allowed me to get into my favourite hobby again. Moreover, &lt;a href=&#34;../the-closure-of-tango&#34;&gt;while I wrote about how demoralised I was over Tango Gameworks&amp;rsquo;s closure&lt;/a&gt;, a factor in the fatigue, some great news happened since - they have been bought and re-opened by Krafton (a South Korean game studio) and brought the Hi-Fi Rush IP with them! Now the spark has really come back. Here is what I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing since:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aylesbury Expedition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/aylesbury-expedition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:21:39 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/aylesbury-expedition/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On 30 July, I went on another photography expedition. I wanted to go to Hastings the day before, but I was late because of some stupid shenanigans back home. £20 down the drain&amp;hellip; I could have tried again, but this time I went to Aylesbury - specifically, walking from Wendover station to Little Kimble station.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I thought my trip was sabotaged, since my planned route was blocked by HS2 construction work. Funny, since HS2 is never fucking happening. But I eventually found a detour and the walk was incredibly satisfying just as I had hoped for.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purfleet Expedition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/purfleet-expedition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 14:55:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/purfleet-expedition/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;London was ~32C yesterday, and good weather like this is perfect for my photo expeditions. This time, I wanted to knock the Purfleet Riverfront/Rainham Marshes/whatever-the-fuck-it&amp;rsquo;s-called. I thought it was rather underwhelming, but I&amp;rsquo;ve had it on my bucket list for a long time, and it&amp;rsquo;s FREE!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Turns out it was more interesting than expected. Great views of the Dartford Crossing, boats passing by the Thames, and other interesting sights. It&amp;rsquo;s outdone by other expeditions that are more vertical and further away from London, but not too bad. One big downside thought was that instead of exploring the marshes, I planned a route from Purfleet to Rainham station. A route that, unbeknownst to me, includes walking near a &lt;em&gt;landfill site&lt;/em&gt;. Disgusting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychotic Episode</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/psychotic-episode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:21:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/psychotic-episode/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am the anti-psychotic,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enough of this. Enough of these _ thoughts. During showers. During family meetings. During my expeditions. During any attempts of media-consumption-cum-escapism. Enough of it. Yet there&amp;rsquo;s no drug that seems to take them away. The fluoxetine does shit. The alprazolam does shit. I don&amp;rsquo;t care what it does anymore. I don&amp;rsquo;t care if it destroys my _ cortex. I&amp;rsquo;ll light up a blunt, snort some _, smoke crack rocks, do anything to stop these thoughts. I&amp;rsquo;ve had these for years and years. Enough. WHEN WILL IT BE ENOUGH?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wetland Expedition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/wetland-expedition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:36:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/wetland-expedition/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../photo-expeditions&#34;&gt;As promised previously&lt;/a&gt;, I went another expedition after seeing the sun out; this time. While listening to the beautiful &lt;em&gt;Wave Race 64&lt;/em&gt; soundtrack, I spent a day at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wwt.org.uk/wetland-centres/london&#34;&gt;WWT London Wetland Centre&lt;/a&gt;. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to call it an &amp;rsquo;expedition&amp;rsquo; when it&amp;rsquo;s still in London, but I recently bought a 70-300mm telephoto lenses, and by God I was going to use it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the results:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/53817946788_e9d1ea1296_c_d.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/53818035704_d05dc69c93_c_d.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/53832119177_b515339d8b_c_d.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wildlife photography is pretty fun, a lot more unique than my usual landscapes. You can see more &lt;a href=&#34;https://flickr.com/blackwavesofenergy/&#34;&gt;on my Flickr&lt;/a&gt; as usual.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meds</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/stopped-medication/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:06:35 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/stopped-medication/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A wise girl once said:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Mental illnesses are like horoscopes, you just look up symptoms that loosely fit your personality.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluoxetine, also known as Prozac, is an SSRI. I&amp;rsquo;ve been on-and-off it for a year and a half now. &lt;em&gt;Consultant&lt;/em&gt; psychiatrist said it was for OCD. However, I&amp;rsquo;m starting to doubt them more and more now. On 60mg of fluoxetine, I see no improvement. Instead, I become unmotivated, and strangely violent. I&amp;rsquo;ve had anger management issues in the past, but I never thought I&amp;rsquo;d have something like that until on this glorified placebo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photo Expeditions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/photo-expeditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:08:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/photo-expeditions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When the sun and its sweet, sweet natural light is out, I feel an urge to go on a photo expedition. What is a photo expedition, you may ask? It&amp;rsquo;s a trip outside of my home town of London, in the rural English countryside, where I spend a day alone taking pictures and listening to my happiest music. With no browser on my phone, there is no need to worry about the state of the world - the outdoors and its photogenicity are all that matters. Examples of such expeditions include:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Fatigue Continues</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/game-fatigue-continues/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 15:22:23 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/game-fatigue-continues/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Day 40 of the Great Gaming Fatigue of 2024. The impact of Tango Gameworks&amp;rsquo;s closing continues to ripple. The only game I &amp;lsquo;play&amp;rsquo; is Super Smash Bros. Ultimate, which I&amp;rsquo;m going to sell today because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to fucking play it anymore, it makes me too mad. I&amp;rsquo;m also selling Dragon Quest XI S on the Nintendo Switch. A game that means a lot to me - it helped get me through my 2019 breakdown and COVID - but I just need to get out of my library to make a quick buck. It&amp;rsquo;s sad&amp;hellip; wait, no it&amp;rsquo;s not, it&amp;rsquo;s just a video game.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Play Videoverse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/play-videoverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:42:21 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/play-videoverse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One day, I decided to check OpenCritic, a Metacritic-like video game rating aggregation site, for the _ hunt for hidden gems. I discovered two highly-rated games that I&amp;rsquo;ve never heard before. One was &amp;lsquo;Vernal Edge&amp;rsquo;, a unique but pretty boring Metroidvania. The other, though, is a contender for one of the greatest pieces of interactive media I&amp;rsquo;ve ever had the luxury of experiencing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Videoverse&lt;/em&gt; is part-social simulation, part-visual novel. Designed as a love letter to old video game message boards and social platforms, &lt;em&gt;Videoverse&lt;/em&gt; revolves around the titular social network, an amalgation of GameSpy and Miiverse.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worried Since 2019</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/worried-since-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:16:08 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/worried-since-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of my biggest faults is that I worry way too much. I think a lot of that has to do with OCD, but after months and months of fluoxetine treatment, I think there&amp;rsquo;s something bigger at play. A lot of the time, my worries are realized. I worried in 2019 about the centralised Web and the existence of algorithmic radicalisation. In worried in 2020 about the impact of COVID. I worried in 2021 and 2022 about post-pandemic malaise, and that virulent populism will surge as a result of widespread vaccine controversy. Haven&amp;rsquo;t many of these worries come true? Doesn&amp;rsquo;t the materialisation of these fears only fuel even stronger anxieties? It feels like a switch was turned on sometime around early 2019, like I switched it on, and all the suffering of the future could be prevented but I can&amp;rsquo;t do anything about it. This sense of helplessness makes me feel that my absence from both social media and real-life interactions is a form of cowardice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pain of Exploits</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-pain-of-exploits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 20:23:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-pain-of-exploits/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t believe this loathsome world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the &lt;a href=&#34;../about-blocklists&#34;&gt;blocklists I mentioned earlier&lt;/a&gt; are incredibly vital for trying to live day to day without the sense of near-apocalyptic dread, there is a certain flaw which I like to call&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;exploits&#34;&gt;EXPLOITS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I heard that some news of one of my favourite games getting downloadable content, but with the &amp;lsquo;Digital Benzodiazepine&amp;rsquo; blocklist added, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t learn anything about it on my main computer. I deleted the browser from my phone, so I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use that either. Like a crack addict needing his next hit, I pondered desperately how to CONSUME this ARBITRARY MEDIA until I found it - my Steam Deck. The Deck uses Linux, but I don&amp;rsquo;t use the desktop mode that often. Going into game mode and browsing through to find the game and the news, I saw something awful - a YouTube link.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phantom Pain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/phantom-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 15:22:50 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/phantom-pain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t updated the blog in a while because I was sick for a while - aches and headaches all over. But today I feel normal. And of course, when there&amp;rsquo;s fever, there&amp;rsquo;s fever dreams. And last night&amp;rsquo;s fever dream was something else.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Basically, I was panicking because of university deadlines. I was thinking to myself, what if I repeat the year &lt;em&gt;again&lt;/em&gt;? How can I be 20+ years and still in university? How many black waves do I have to suffer to achieve my education? I imagined the student debt piling up, receiving no honours by the end of the year due to poor performance and having my CVs shredded, the image of the campus being burned in my retinas for eternity, just a nightmare of educational bureaucracy suffocating me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Black Waves</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/other/the-black-waves/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:24:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/other/the-black-waves/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the beginning of 2023, I brought a sparkling new Macbook Pro and a subscription to &lt;em&gt;Day One&lt;/em&gt;, and started a blog - &lt;em&gt;Magdi Battles the Black Waves&lt;/em&gt;. It was intended to last for a year, but I only managed to keep track until August.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/0HakH0D.png&#34; alt=&#34;Magdi-Fights-the-Black-Waves.pdf&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This was intended not for entertainment, but to help me manage my life. &lt;em&gt;bwoe&lt;/em&gt; stands for &amp;lsquo;Black Waves of Energy&amp;rsquo;. What are black waves of energy? It&amp;rsquo;s quite hard to explain, but&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photography at the London MCM Expo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/photography-at-mcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:57:54 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/photography-at-mcm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last weekend was Comic Con day, and I know what that meant - lots and lots of cosplay photography to practice my portraits. Last year I went on a Friday, but today I decided to go on a Saturday. Big mistake. The venue was absolutely packed, completely crowded with cosplayers. You&amp;rsquo;d think this would be a good thing, but since Saturday opens very early (9am), I didn&amp;rsquo;t get much sleep. The lack of sleep to wake up for priority opening means less energy (and nerves&amp;hellip;) to ask for photos, plus the over-excess of cosplayers making my head spin. Had I stuck to the Friday date, I would have more energy and less cosplayers, meaning a shorter checklist and more chances to check.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About My Blocklists</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/about-blocklists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 16:39:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/about-blocklists/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In an &lt;a href=&#34;../the-internet-is-hell&#34;&gt;earlier post&lt;/a&gt;, I explained how I used Cold Turkey Blocker to keep me sane. Today I&amp;rsquo;ll go over the blocklists I use and how I cycle between them for maximum efficiency and sanity-preservation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Digital Duloxetine&#xA;This blocklist is permanent, 24/7, until Cold Turkey is uninstalled (in other words, a system reset). It consists of of over 500 websites, ranging from garbage clickbait sites to pornography to central social media platforms to news outlets and beyond. There is no way to access these sites, so I can&amp;rsquo;t access them whatsoever. Good!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See My Photos at Flickr!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/my-flickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:14:50 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/my-flickr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/PlD5ZoP.png&#34; alt=&#34;Flickr Showcase&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;httpswwwflickrcomblackwavesofenergy&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/blackwavesofenergy&#34;&gt;https://www.flickr.com/blackwavesofenergy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still Fatigued</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/still-fatigued/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 17:25:17 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/still-fatigued/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been about a week since &lt;a href=&#34;../the-closure-of-tango&#34;&gt;my rant about the closure of Tango Gameworks&lt;/a&gt;, and while I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten over it a bit, I&amp;rsquo;m still fatigued by gaming. With the announcement of the Switch successor, we&amp;rsquo;re inching towards a proper new generation of gaming, but it&amp;rsquo;s hard to be excited. Constant layoffs and studio closures. Rising prices and a trend towards $70 games. Cheaper budget games taken hostage by the whims of what popular streamers decide to play. The gaming community has never been the friendliest, but now it&amp;rsquo;s loaded with dissatisfaction and borderline hatred against the industry, an IQ-dropping culture war battleground, and general pessimism all round. It&amp;rsquo;s ugly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Closure of Tango Gameworks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/the-closure-of-tango/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 18:20:23 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/the-closure-of-tango/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In early 2023, I felt like gaming wasn&amp;rsquo;t fun anymore. I knew it was a common fatigue though, and that there&amp;rsquo;ll be a game that I&amp;rsquo;ll play soon that would inject that fun and soul only the medium could provide. That happened when &lt;em&gt;Hi-Fi Rush&lt;/em&gt; shadow dropped in January 2023. With its gorgeous &lt;em&gt;Futurama&lt;/em&gt;-esque aesthetics and comedic tone and excellent reviews, I bought it and fell in love immediately. The catharsis of the character action and rhythm genres, joined at last in spectacular fashion. It cured my fatigue. In 2023, despite sharing my time with work, photography, and vacations with my family, I completed an 70 video games thanks to my renewed love of gaming attributed to &lt;em&gt;Hi-Fi Rush&lt;/em&gt; (not to mention that 2023 was a great year for gaming in general).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Internet Is Hell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-internet-is-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:42:48 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/net/the-internet-is-hell/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;God bless &lt;a href=&#34;https://getcoldturkey.com/&#34;&gt;Cold Turkey Blocker&lt;/a&gt;. What would I do without you? Well, live in a more honest world, an honestly shittier world. In my blocklist called &amp;lsquo;Digital Alprazolam&amp;rsquo; which lasts for the end of time and cannot be deactivated without uninstalling Cold Turkey. I have blocked 500+ sites, including popular social media psyop tools like Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn and the like. If I need to apply for a job with LinkedIn, then I&amp;rsquo;ll stay unemployed, thank you very much.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citra and Yuzu are gone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/citra-yuzu-gone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 23:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/citra-yuzu-gone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, damn. It was &lt;a href=&#34;../flatpak-emu-problems&#34;&gt;literally just yesterday&lt;/a&gt; that I uploaded about emulation problems, but now we have a different type of emulation problem: Citra and Yuzu are gone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/ICEr3ig.png&#34; alt=&#34;y&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is relevant because I was talking about a fatal bug for Dolphin, which also affected Citra (and RPCS3). The fix for Citra was uploaded LITERALLY YESTERDAY, meaning had the Citra/Yuzu team (the same dev team) hadn&amp;rsquo;t updated it, the last version of Citra on Flathub would be forever unbootable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flatpak Emu Problems of March 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/flatpak-emu-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:09:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/flatpak-emu-problems/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So recently, there was some bizarre emulation problems. The issue didn&amp;rsquo;t come with the Steam Deck, or EmuDeck, but with the emulators themselves, specifically the Flatpak version commonly used in Linux.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dolphin, RPCS3, and Citra all were nonfunctional out of nowhere. Citra was quickly patched, but Dolphin and RPCS3 are still unable to boot as of this post. Booting them reveals no error message or dumped log. Booting them via CLI (i.e. &lt;code&gt;flatpak run org.DolphinEmu.dolphin-emu&lt;/code&gt;) gives you the following message:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings for Citra</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/game/citra-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/game/citra-settings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Playing 3DS games on a single screen can be tough. The vertical form factor of the 3DS makes gaming quite the challenge when emulating. So, these are my preferred Citra settings. Feel free to use or improve them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;picross-3d&#34;&gt;Picross 3D&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Main screen: bottom&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Other screen: small or disabled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use a mouse and keyboard for this one, with d-pad and L buttons being used for controls. Other screen is not required.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 16:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello World!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;tables-of-contents&#34;&gt;Tables of Contents&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#headers&#34;&gt;Headers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#emphasis&#34;&gt;Emphasis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#lists&#34;&gt;Lists&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#links-and-images&#34;&gt;Links and Images&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#code-blocks&#34;&gt;Code Blocks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#blockquotes&#34;&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#tables&#34;&gt;Tables&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#horizontal-rules&#34;&gt;Horizontal Rules&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#line-breaks&#34;&gt;Line Breaks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#escaping-characters&#34;&gt;Escaping Characters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#inline-html&#34;&gt;Inline HTML&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#task-lists&#34;&gt;Task Lists&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#subscripts-and-superscripts&#34;&gt;Subscripts and Superscripts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#footnotes&#34;&gt;Footnotes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#automatic-url-linking&#34;&gt;Automatic URL Linking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#strikethrough&#34;&gt;Strikethrough&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#tables-of-contents&#34;&gt;Tables of Contents&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;headers&#34;&gt;Headers&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;header-1&#34;&gt;Header 1&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;header-2&#34;&gt;Header 2&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;header-3&#34;&gt;Header 3&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;header-4&#34;&gt;Header 4&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;emphasis&#34;&gt;Emphasis&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bold&lt;/em&gt; text. &lt;em&gt;Italic&lt;/em&gt; text. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bold and italic&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;lists&#34;&gt;Lists&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ordered list item 1.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ordered list item 2.&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Unordered list item 1&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Unordered list item 2&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;links-and-images&#34;&gt;Links and Images&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com&#34;&gt;Link to Google&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://markdown-here.com/img/icon256.png&#34; alt=&#34;Markdown Logo&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
