<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photo-Stuff on bwoe</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/photo-stuff/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photo-Stuff on bwoe</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:36:27 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/photo-stuff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wetland Expedition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/wetland-expedition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:36:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/wetland-expedition/</guid>
      <description>As promised previously, I went another expedition after seeing the sun out; this time. While listening to the beautiful Wave Race 64 soundtrack, I spent a day at the WWT London Wetland Centre. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to call it an &amp;rsquo;expedition&amp;rsquo; when it&amp;rsquo;s still in London, but I recently bought a 70-300mm telephoto lenses, and by God I was going to use it.&#xA;Here&amp;rsquo;s the results:&#xA;Wildlife photography is pretty fun, a lot more unique than my usual landscapes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photo Expeditions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/photo-expeditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:08:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/photo-expeditions/</guid>
      <description>When the sun and its sweet, sweet natural light is out, I feel an urge to go on a photo expedition. What is a photo expedition, you may ask? It&amp;rsquo;s a trip outside of my home town of London, in the rural English countryside, where I spend a day alone taking pictures and listening to my happiest music. With no browser on my phone, there is no need to worry about the state of the world - the outdoors and its photogenicity are all that matters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photography at the London MCM Expo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/photography-at-mcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:57:54 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/photography-at-mcm/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend was Comic Con day, and I know what that meant - lots and lots of cosplay photography to practice my portraits. Last year I went on a Friday, but today I decided to go on a Saturday. Big mistake. The venue was absolutely packed, completely crowded with cosplayers. You&amp;rsquo;d think this would be a good thing, but since Saturday opens very early (9am), I didn&amp;rsquo;t get much sleep. The lack of sleep to wake up for priority opening means less energy (and nerves&amp;hellip;) to ask for photos, plus the over-excess of cosplayers making my head spin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See My Photos at Flickr!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/my-flickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:14:50 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/photo/my-flickr/</guid>
      <description>&#xA;https://www.flickr.com/blackwavesofenergy </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
